### Contact

smcguff87@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sheenamcguffey-0044156b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

ACLS TNCC BLS

### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

# Sheena McGuffey

BSN CCRN ICU Registered Nurse at Missouri Baptist Medical Center

Saint Louis, Missouri

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse Emergency Department with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Critical Care, Hospitals, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), and Emergency Medicine. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Nursing from University of Kentucky.

## Experience

Missouri Baptist Medical Center 4 years ICU Registered Nurse July 2016 - Present (4 years)

Intensive Care Nurse
July 2016 - Present (4 years)
Greater St. Louis Area

St. Anthony's Medical Center
Emergency Department RN
December 2013 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Manage care to 3 adult patient's in the ER--- The level of trauma ranges from Level 1-4, even though St.Anthony's is a level 2, we do get several Level 1. Manage care to 4 pediatric patients at one time

Baptist Health Louisville Surgical ICU RN January 2013 - December 2013 (1 year) Lexinton

## Education

University of Kentucky BSN, Nursing · (2008 - 2011)